MUNSEONG JEONG

M: 0452462858 E: jmunseng@gmail.com Carlton, VIC 3053

Portfolio: https://www.leonjeong.com/

A fast learner and a passionate programmer with around one years of frontend experience. I am experienced in front-end development using numerous programming languages/tools including HTML, CSS, JS, React, NodeJS, Java, MySQL and Git. I enjoy learning new languages and development techniques. My communication and teamwork skills have improved a lot from previous working experience. I also adapt quickly to different working environments and I am a good team player that received many positive feedback from colleagues.

EXPERIENCE

Rider Operations

Oct 2019 - Present

EASI Australia pty Itd

Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

EASI Australia is running the most popular Asian food delivery platform in Australia. My responsibilities were:

- managed about 200 riders in Australia to help the platform to improve order capacity;
- helped riders to solve different issues they have during work;
- solved the conflicts and communication problems among merchants, riders and customers;
- improved communication and teamwork skills.

Online Store Manager

May 2015 - Sep 2017

DamingGlass

Pocheon, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

DamingGlass is a global trading company. The core business is the purchase, shipping, and sale of original glass sheets from China to Korea. My responsibilities were:

- developed online shopping platform from scratch based on WordPress and Cafe24 to enable customers to order products and track orders online, mainly used PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript;
- managed product information on different e-commerce platforms, such as Naver shopping, Gmarket and 11 street store, including creating images via Photoshop;
- translated documents between Chinese and Korean.

Web Designer 샵피라 (Sappira)

Jul 2013 - Apr 2014

Uijeongbu, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

Sappira is a company that designs, produces, and sells clothing for medical and entertainment companies in Korea. My responsibilities were:

- created and maintained promotion web pages, mainly used PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript;
- maintained product content across different online shopping platforms, including editing product information and creating photos via Photoshop;

Front-End Web Developer KISKorea

Feb 2012 - Apr 2013 Seoul, Korea

Kiskorea provides an online international tourism platform and a mobile gaming platform. My responsibilities were:

- coded and maintained static web pages from the design, including both tourism and mobile gaming platforms' user interface pages and admin management pages, mainly based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and W2UI;
- implemented functionalities that get data from database, mainly based on Java and MySQL;
- tested, debugged and fixed errors in web applications.

PROJECTS

Cloud Task - Task Platform

Oct 2020

It is a university project. The platform enables users to create and view tasks (in both list and detail pages) in the application. Users can receive email notification after registering. Mainly used React,, Express, MongoDB and Node.js.

EDUCATION

Graduate Certificate of Business Analytics

Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

Kaplan BUSINESS SCHOOL Dockland

Majors: Business Analytics

Bachelor of Information Technology

Mar 2018 - Nov 2020

Deakin University, Burwood Majors: Application Development

Web Developer Employment Program

2011 - 2012

Deojoeun Computer Art Academy(Seoul, Korea)

SKILLS

Programming Languages/Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, JQuery,

Bootstrap, C, C#, Python, numpy, Java, **Databases**: MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB

Source Control: Git, GitHub

IDE: Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, EditPlus

Communication Skills: communicate effectively in English, Mandarin and Korean.